Guide to the Afrika Bambaataa hip hop archive, circa 1972-2016.
Bambaataa, Afrika hip hop archive,
- Series IX. Music Collection
  - 12 inch Vinyl
    - Not annotated
      - P
        - Pure Energy - Too hot, 1982; SR-28459; Pure Energy (Box 399)
          Catalog # PDS 445; A-side Matrix # HERBIE Jr Hi LORRAINE (E.O.)-DL IT'S HOT PDS-445A140,045
        - Pure Soul - I want you back, 1995; SR-28460; Pure Soul (Box 399)
          Catalog # DMD 2261; A-side Matrix # ST-DM-79366-79824-79730-A-1 HFM 95
        - Pure Soul - We must be in love, 1995; SR-28461; Pure Soul (Box 399)
          Catalog # DMD 2236; A-side Matrix # STDM-77921-77922-1
        - Pyramid Project - II, 2000; SR-28471; Pyramid Project (Box 399)
          Catalog # WL 002; A-side Matrix # 43721 A
          Wicked Lakes Records
        - Pyramids - Birth-speed-merging, 1976; SR-28462; Pyramids (Box 399)
          Catalog # BB 30935; A-side Matrix # MASTERED BY CAPITOL BB-1-30935-J-1
          Pyramid Records
        - P$C - 25 to life (Disc one), 2005; SR-28463; P$C (Box 399)
          Catalog # 83797-1; A-side Matrix # 83797-1A CS J.Y.
        - P$C - 25 to life (Disc two), 2005; SR-28464; P$C (Box 399)
          Catalog # 83797-1; A-side Matrix # 83797-1C
        - P$C - 25 to life (Disc one), 2005; SR-28465; P$C (Box 399)
        - P$C - 25 to life (Disc two), 2005; SR-28466; P$C (Box 399)
        - P$C - I'm a king, 2005; SR-28467; P$C; T.I.; Lil Scrappy (Box 399)
          Catalog # PR 301856; A-side Matrix # PRCD 301856-1AB A
        - Parliament - Trombipulation, 1980; SR-28469; Parliament (Box 399)
          Catalog # NBLP 7249; A-side Matrix # A-1 NBLP-7249-AS K-1 MASTERED AT ALLEN ZENTZ L.A., CALIF.
        - Patten, Dee - Who's the bad man, 1992; SR-28468; Patten, Dee (Box 399)
          Catalog # HAND 003T; A-side Matrix # HAND-003T-A1 MAX
        - Patterson, Kellee - Let go, let go (let love be the driver); How I love your smile, 1979; SR-28470; Patterson, Kellee (Box 399)
          Catalog # SD12-006; A-side Matrix # SB-12-006-A GRT1 GRT
          Shadybrook Records
        - Planet Patrol - Play at your own risk, 1992; SR-28472; Planet Patrol (Box 399)
          Catalog #; A-side Matrix # PUTA A (RE)
          Puta Records
        - Park Avenue - Slow motion, 1982; SR-30409; Park Avenue (Box 399)
          Catalog # DMD 356; A-side Matrix # STDM 43362-1 1-1
        - Please - Manila thriller, 1976; SR-30880; Please (Box 376)
          Catalog # PS 672; A-side Matrix # XZAL 14499 BG ST
          London Records
        - Preluxe - You're the one for me, 1998; SR-13966; Preluxe; Griffin, Clive; "D" Train (Box 376)
          Catalog # PRE 001; A-side Matrix # PRE-001-A
          Preluxe
        - Plastyc Buddha - String vybe, 2002; SR-30956; Plastyc Buddha (Box 147)
          In same jacket as # SR-30957. Multiple copies.
          Catalog # 541416 500803; A-side Matrix # 54 14 16 500 803 A1
          Life Enhancing Audio
          Ghent, Belgium
        - Plastyc Buddha - String vybe, 2002; SR-30957; Plastyc Buddha (Box 147)
          In same jacket as # SR-30956. Multiple copies.
        - Pointer Sisters - I need you, 1983; SR-30958; Pointer Sisters (Box 147)